# Kayo de Lima Kalinauskas

Address: 430 Alexandrino da Silveira Bueno Street, Cambuci Neighborhood, São Paulo - SP.

Phone: +55 (17) 99265 · 0014

kalinauskas@live.com

linkedin.com/in/kayokalinauskas github.com/kayokalinauskas

#### Goal:

Front-End/Full Stack Developer

#### **Summary of Qualifications**

With 8 years of experience in IT and ERP, I work as a programmer with experience in developing web applications, knowledge in several technologies and concepts, such as React, Angular, Javascript, NodeJS, Express, Api Rest, HTML. JQuery, Ajax, CSS, Sass, Bootstrap, Tailwind, Styled Components, WPO, SEO, Docker, Jenkins, PostgreSQL, Unit Tests, Git, C#, Agile Methodologies, among others. I have solid knowledge in development techniques, as well as the ability to work in teams, meet deadlines and overcome challenges.

#### **Work Experience**

## **OCTO Tecnologia e Consultoria**

Position: Software Developer.

08/2021 - 01/2023.

As a front-end developer I worked in internal and external projects performing maintenance and creating new features to improve the user experience, with different stacks using Javascript, HTML, CSS, Boostrap, JQuery, Ajax, among others.

Acting front-end with Angular and back-end in C# in the maintenance and creation of modules of an ICMS credit recovery system for a client in the accounting segment.

Worked in ERP systems using React, ASP.NET and C# in order to maintain the system and create new features for internal system users of Multidrogas chain, Kingcase stores, among other companies.

#### **OCTO Tecnologia e Consultoria**

Position: Technical Support Coordinator.

08/2020 - 08/2021

As coordinator, I held meetings with customers to discover the needs of the companies, analyze the entire sales journey to enable the customization and molding of the system in order to deliver the best solution for the customer.

After system validation, I performed technical training with all the customer's staff.

Coordinating a team of 5 internal support technicians, I was responsible for training the concepts used in ERP systems, such as: sales module, stock, CRM, NF-e, CF-e, among others.

I also monitored the customer service provided by the team, and performed technical analysis and implementation of solutions.

#### Freelance Developer

03/2018 - 08/2020

Development of landing pages and web applications involving technologies such as: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, jQuery.

#### **Hipertec Sistemas**

Position: Technical Support Analyst.

01/2015 - 06/2018

As an analyst, I provided customer service with the objective of solving problems in ERP systems.

#### **Academic Background**

**Computer Science - in progress** 

Universidade Anhembi Morumbi

#### Languages

Advanced English (reading, writing and speaking).

### **Professional Development**

- RocketSeat Ignite (React, Nextjs, GraphQL, Node, Typescript)
- C# Complete POO (Sintax, POO, ASP .NET, Entity Framework, MVC)
- Angular The Complete Guide (Angular13, Módulos, arquiteturas, RxJS, NgRx, RestApis, routing)

#### Other skills

• **ERP:** Tax Knowledge (ICMS, ST, CFOP, IPI, PIS, COFINS, GNRE, SAT, CC-e, NF-e, CT-e, SPED, tax classifications, manifests and the like), knowledge of tax calculation, Sales, Inventory, Financial Modules (accounts receivable, payable and cash flow), Product datasheet, NF-e management, band disable, integration with API's and Web Services.

#### **Volunteer Work**

 Basic computer teacher for children at the NGO Associação Anjo da Guarda in São José do Rio Preto - SP, 2015.